NNENNA NDUKWE

832-484-9125 Innenna.s.ndukwe@gmail.com

Detail oriented and versatile Computer Science student with an interest in software engineering and a career goal of specializing in Artificial Intelligence, Deep Learning, and Automation as a Machine Learning Software Engineer. Creative and logical with experience in programming, software projects and web/app development. Experience in full-stack programming, social service, IT, academic, retail, and customer service fields.

- JavaScript development
- Youth Development & Mentorship
- IT Tutoring

- HTML5/CSS3, Bootstrap 4
- Consulting/Sales
- Java, VB.NET
- Python development
- Technical Writing
- Customer Service

EDUCATION

Boston University | Boston, MA

COMPUTER SCIENCE 2020

Relevant Coursework: Honors Program with University of Massachusetts Amherst

Fall 2016 - Present

Ethics in Information in Technology, Computer Science I, Data Structures & Algorithms, Computer Science II

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

RESILIENT CODERS | BOSTON, MA

Sep 2017 - Present

Full Stack Web Developer

- Mongo Database, Express.js, React, Node.js, Pure JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, jQuery, Vue.js, Angular.js
- 15+ projects over 4-month span as contracted collaborative development
- Mobile, Software system, & Web Application development implementations
- Client-side and server-side programming for scalable, agile development

COMMON SENSING | Cambridge, MA

Sep 2017- Present

Full Stack Web & Software Developer

- Develop internal software for device production with Python 3.x & statistical linear regression models
- Utilize React, D3.js JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, JSX to engineer web application data visualization systems
- Debug, test, calibrate, engineer, and upgrade firmware versions for medical device product pipelining

COMMON SENSING | Cambridge, MA

June 2017 - Sep 2017

Product & Software Engineering Intern

- Internal software development for insulin
- Testing iOS & Android applications, bug fixing, version control, code reviewing, and pair programming
- Automate engineering software tools for quality metrics and firmware accuracy/productivity
- Managing database of 10,000+ records for data analyses to determine product efficacy for clinical research
- Perform product performance testing, inspection, calibration, software upgrades, and Quality Control

ROXBURY COMMUNITY COLLEGE | ROXBURY, MA

Aug 2016 - June 2017

IT Computer Laboratory Assistant

- Responsible for maintaining 50+ computers and performing periodic software updates
- Provide assistance to 50+ students by handling questions & problems in a courteous, efficient manner
- Teach and guide student groups in using software such as Microsoft Word, Excel, Access & PowerPoint
- Tutor English, writing and essay articulation for ESL students in the Writing Lab via appointments

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

GIRL DEVELOP IT | Boston, MA

Oct 2017 - Present

Technical Teacher Assistant Volunteer

Technical Assistant Instructor Volunteer

Nov 2016 - Present

BLACK GIRLS CODE | Boston, MA

- Oversee monthly coding classes for a 30+ girls between the ages of 8 and 17.
 - Facilitate developmental and leadership workshops with kid coding software Kodu Game Lab
 - Utilize fundamental Java/C++ Computer Science programming functions for kid programming